// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The following is the three states of matter, EXCEPT..",
    answer: "fiber",
    options: [
      "Gas",
      "fiber",
      "Liquid ",
      "Solid "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A liquid-to-vapour phase transition can be shown in the van der Waals model of a fluid.",
    answer: "Van der Waals model",
    options: [
      "Coulombs Law",
      "Kinetic Molecular Theory",
      "Chemical properties",
      "Van der Waals model"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "True or False: Energy, light, and sound are not classified as matter.",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False",
      ".",
      "."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "a state of matter that has definite shape and definite volume.",
    answer: "Solid",
    options: [
      "Chemical changes",
      "Saturated Solution",
      "Solid",
      "Sinigang Mix"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " a state of matter that can flow and have definite volume and does not have a specific shape like a solid.",
    answer: "Liquid",
    options: [
      "Matabang",
      "Chemical changes",
      "Concentrated Solution",
      "Liquid "
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 6,
    question: "a state of matter that has no fixed shape and no fixed volume.",
    answer: "Gas",
    options: [
      "Crystalline Solid",
      "Physical changes",
      "Gas",
      "Rubic's Cube"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "have fixed volume but no fixed shape.",
    answer: "Liquid",
    options: [
      "Liquid",
      "Kinetic Energy",
      "Chemical changes",
      "Garter"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 8,
    question: "An example of gases.",
    answer: "oxygen",
    options: [
      "digestion",
      "oxygen",
      "hardness",
      "colour"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "An example of solids.",
    answer: "Chemical properties",
    options: [
      "oxygen",
      "Chemical properties",
      "rock",
      "Vapour Pressure"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 10,
    question: "Force of attraction between particles is adamant.",
    answer: "solid",
    options: [
      "Acidity",
      "solid",
      "toxicity ",
      "Nucleus"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The kinetic energy of particles is higher than in Liquids.",
    answer: "Gas",
    options: [
      "Gas",
      "Anisotrophic",
      "solid",
      "rust"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 12,
    question: "Theytake the shape of the container in which they are kept.",
    answer: "Liquid",
    options: [
      "solid",
      "wood",
      "Intramolecular Forces",
      "Liquid"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "have neither a fixed volume nor a fixed shape.",
    answer: "Gas",
    options: [
      "Solid",
      "Chemical changes",
      "amorphous",
      "Gas"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 14,
    question: "particles are less tightly packed as compared to solids.",
    answer: "Liquid",
    options: [
      "Experiment",
      "Liquid",
      "Physical changes",
      "wood"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The particles are less tightly packed as compared to solids.",
    answer: "Solid",
    options: [
      "Chemical properties",
      "Solid",
      "H2o",
      "water"
    ]
  },
]